Inventory of the American National Red Cross records
Hoover Institution Archives
- Commission for France, 1915-1922
  - Oeuvre des Mères et des Enfants de la Guerre, 1920-1921
    Box/Folder 80: 11
  - Oeuvre des Orphhelins Agricoles du Pas-de-Calais, 1920-1921
    Box/Folder 80: 12
  - L'Ouvroir de Permanence de Charmes, 1920-1921
    Box/Folder 80: 13
  - Bureau Polonais de Rapatriement, Paris, 1919-1921
    Box/Folder 80: 14
  - Orphelinat de l'Adoration Perpétuelle, Brest, 1920-1921
    Box/Folder 80: 15-16
  - Oeuvre des Petits Parisiens, 1921
    Box/Folder 80: 17
  - Lt. Colonel Robert Olds, reports, 1920-1921
    Box/Folder 80: 18
  - Memorandum for Major Perkins, 1917
    Box/Folder 80: 19
  - Bureau of personnel, 1918-1921
    Box/Folder 80: 20-24
  - Pétain Fund for French Wounded, reports, 1917-1918
    Box/Folder 80: 25. Includes letters of appreciation from the members of the Sénat, Chambre des Députés, various conseils généraux
  - Pétain Fund for French Wounded, reports, 1917-1918 (Reel 110)
    Box/Folder 80: 26-28
  - Petites Soeurs de l'Assomption, 1920-1921
    Box/Folder 80: 29
  - Le Phare de France, Paris, 1919
    Box/Folder 80: 30
  - Bureau of Photography, report, 1919
    Box/Folder 80: 31
  - Le Placement Familial, Paris, 1920
    Box/Folder 80: 32
  - Bureau of Refugees and Relief, 1918
    Box/Folder 80: 33
  - Poland and Polish Red Cross, 1920-1921
    Box/Folder 80: 34-35
  - Polish White Cross, 1919
    Box/Folder 80: 36
  - Base Polonaise, 1919
    Box/Folder 80: 37
  - Camp Pontezen, reports, 1918-1919
    Box/Folder 81: 1
  - Pour l'Enfance et la Famille par l'Aide Sociale, 1919-1921
    Box/Folder 81: 2-3
  - Sister ruling, 1918
    Box/Folder 81: 4
  - Department de la Somme, report, 1919-1920
    Box/Folder 81: 5-6
  - War Orphans, department of Stars and Stripes, Paris, reports, correspondence, sample cases, 1918-1922
    Box/Folder 81: 7-14
  - War Orphans, department of Stars and Stripes, Paris, reports, correspondence, sample cases, 1918-1922 (Reel 111)
    Box/Folder 81: 15-21
  - Studios for portrait masks, 1919
    Box/Folder 81: 22-24
  - Medical and surgical supplies, reports, 1917-1919
    Box/Folder 81: 25-26
  - Syrian cases, reports, 1920
    Box/Folder 81: 27
  - Director of transportation Major C.G. Osborne, reports from tours, 1919
    Box/Folder 81: 28
  - Transportation Department, reports, 1919-1920
    Box/Folder 81: 29-32
  - Oeuvre de la Préservation Antituberculeuse de l'Enfant, 1919
    Box/Folder 81: 33
  - Program, 1920-1921 (Reel 112)
    Box/Folder 82: 1
  - Prisoners and refugees of war, 1920-1921
    Box/Folder 82: 2-5
  - Société pour la Protection de la Réforme no. 2, 1918-1919
    Box/Folder 82: 6
  - Les Pupilles de la Nation, 1920
    Box/Folder 82: 7
  - Publicity, 1920-1922
    Box/Folder 82: 8-11
  - Bureau for Reconstruction and Reeducation, 1918-1919
    Box/Folder 82: 12
  - Recreation hunts at hospital points, 1918-1919 (Reel 113)
    Box/Folder 82: 13
  - Bureau of Refugees and Relief, 1918
    Box/Folder 82: 14
  - Real estate, 1919
    Box/Folder 82: 15
  - Reports, 1918-1921
    Box/Folder 82: 16-22
  - La Résidence Sociale, 1920-1921
    Box/Folder 82: 23
  - Robberies and thefts, report, 1919
    Box/Folder 82: 24
  - Rockefeller Foundation, 1918-1920
    Box/Folder 82: 25
  - Roosevelt Memorial, 1919
    Box/Folder 82: 26
  - Headquarters at Rouen, news service, July 14, 1919
    Box/Folder 82: 27
  - Operation of rest stations at aviation schools and supplies depots, general instruction, 1918
    Box/Folder 82: 28
  - Le Retour au Foyer, 1917-1919
    Box/Folder 82: 29
  - Le Retour à Reims, 1921
    Box/Folder 82: 30
  - Sale of Red Cross Goods, 1917-1918
    Box/Folder 82: 31
  - Le Secours de Guerre, 1919
    Box/Folder 82: 32
  - Instruction to searchers attached to hospitals or Army Divisions, 1918
    Box/Folder 82: 33
  - Le Secours d'Urgence, 1918-1920
    Box/Folder 82: 34
  - Chicago training camp, 1918
    Box/Folder 83: 1
  - Secrétariat Français des Villages Libérés, 1921
    Box/Folder 83: 2
  - Secretary General, reports, 1918
    Box/Folder 83: 3
  - Serbian refugees in France, a summary of conditions and recommendations prepared by the Bureau of Tuberculosis, Department of Civil Affairs, ARC, Paris, 1918
    Box/Folder 83: 4
  - Shipping arrangements to France, 1917, 1920
    Box/Folder 83: 5
  - Shurtleff Fund, 1919
    Box/Folder 83: 6
  - Service social, Paris, 1919-1921
    Box/Folder 83: 7
  - Sightseeing--Convalescents, 1918
    Box/Folder 83: 8
  - Transportation Department designated shipments, 1917-1918
    Box/Folder 83: 9
  - Transportation Department tonnage space for shipments from United States, 1917
    Box/Folder 83: 10
  - Transportation Department bulletins, 1920-1921
    Box/Folder 83: 11
  - Transportation Department reports, 1920-1921 (Reel 114)
    Box/Folder 83: 12
  - Bureau of Tuberculosis, 1918-1919
    Box/Folder 83: 13
  - Edward Tuck, powdered milk for refugee babies, 1919
    Box/Folder 83: 14
  - Uniforms and clothing, 1917-1918
    Box/Folder 83: 15-17
  - Union des Femmes de France, 1919-1920
    Box/Folder 83: 18-19
  - U.S. Army, information on draft, 1917
    Box/Folder 83: 20
  - War Orphans Bureau, reports, 1920-1921
    Box/Folder 83: 21
  - Operation of base warehouses, instructions, 1918
    Box/Folder 83: 22
  - National headquarters, Washington, correspondence, 1917-1919
    Box/Folder 83: 23-24
  - French Wounded Emergency Fund, Casper Whitney, 1915-1916
    Box/Folder 83: 25
  - Edith war charities, 1917
    Box/Folder 83: 26
  - Women's Wharton War Relief Corps, 1917-1918 (Reel 115)
    Box/Folder 83: 27-29
  - Smith College Relief Unit, 1920-1921
    Box/Folder 83: 30
  - YMCA, relief work, reports, 1918-1920
    Box/Folder 84: 1-3
  - Temporary field organization for devastated regions, 1918
    Box/Folder 84: 4
  - Operation of zone stores, 1918
    Box/Folder 84: 5
- Commission for Switzerland, 1917-1922
  - Classification of accounts, 1919
    Box/Folder 84: 6
  - American Army, general, 1917-1919
    Box/Folder 84: 7
  - Legation of the United States of America, Berne, 1917-1918
    Box/Folder 84: 8
  - Relief to Americans, 1919
    Box/Folder 84: 9
  - The American War Relief Society of Geneva, 1918
    Box/Folder 84: 10
  - Application forms for employment, 1918
    Box/Folder 84: 11
  - Appropriation, Paris, 1918-1919
    Box/Folder 84: 12
  - Austrian investigation, 1918
    Box/Folder 84: 13
  - American women in Basel, 1918
    Box/Folder 84: 14
  - Office in Berne, reports, 1918-1919
    Box/Folder 84: 15
  - Bolshevik activities in Switzerland under the cover of ARC, 1919
    Box/Folder 84: 16
  - Bureau of Finance and Accounts, 1918
    Box/Folder 84: 17
  - Bureau International Féministe de Renseignements, 1918
    Box/Folder 84: 18
  - Canteens in Berne, 1918
    Box/Folder 84: 19
  - Civilian Relief Department, reports, 1917-1919
    Box/Folder 84: 20
  - Civilian Relief Department, reports, 1917-1919 (Reel 116)
    Box/Folder 84: 21-28
  - Commissioner for Belgium Ernest P. Bicknell, reports, 1918-1919
    Box/Folder 84: 29-30
  - Children relief, lists of children, 1917-1919
    Box/Folder 85: 1-3
  - Children relief, reports, 1918-1919
    Box/Folder 85: 4-6
  - Children's photographs and thank you letters, 1917
    Box/Folder 85: 7-9. Photographs and letters from French children related to relief in France.
  - Children's photographs and thank you letters, 1917 (Reel 117)
    Box/Folder 85: 10-13
  - Rapport Général de l'Oeuvre des Réfugiés Belges en Suisse, Lausanne, 1917
    Box/Folder 85: 14
  - Hospital and convalescent home in Fribourg, 1918
    Box/Folder 85: 15
  - Other organizations, reports, memoranda, 1917-1919
    Box/Folder 85: 16-20
  - Milka Alpina, Société Anonyme, 1918
    Box/Folder 85: 21
  - Le Bonheur Familial, 1917-1919 (Reel 118)
    Box/Folder 85: 22
  - Evacuees, reports, 1918-1919
    Box/Folder 86: 1-2
  - Italian Commission, 1918-1919
    Box/Folder 86: 3-4
  - Lithuanian Central Committee, 1917-1918
    Box/Folder 86: 5
  - Legation of Luxemburg, 1914, 1917
    Box/Folder 86: 6
  - Montenegrin Legation, 1917
    Box/Folder 86: 7
  - Oeuvre des Ouvriers à la Montagne
    Box/Folder 86: 8
  - Greek refugees, 1918-1919
    Box/Folder 86: 9
  - Orphans, 1918-1919
    Box/Folder 86: 10
  - Personal record of work done in the ARC by Walter J. Marcley, M.D., February 20, 1918-April 15, 1919
    Box/Folder 86: 11
  - Tuberculosis refugees, 1918-1919
    Box/Folder 86: 12-14
  - Romanian refugees, 1918-1919 (Reel 119)
    Box/Folder 86: 15-18
  - Russian refugees, 1918-1919
    Box/Folder 86: 19-21
  - Polish refugees, Polish-American Committee, 1918-1919
    Box/Folder 86: 22-23
  - Polish refugees, Polish Warsaw Committee, 1917-1918
    Box/Folder 86: 24
  - Polish refugees, Polish Vevey Committee, 1918
    Box/Folder 86: 25
  - Polish refugees, Milk for Polish children, 1918
    Box/Folder 86: 26
  - Polish refugees, Investigation reports, 1918
    Box/Folder 86: 27
  - Commission for Relief in Belgium, 1918 (Reel 120)
    Box/Folder 87: 1
  - Comité Central des Sociétés des Citoyens Russes en Suisse, 1919
    Box/Folder 87: 2
  - Comité Genevois de Secours aux Russes Résidant en Suisse, letters of thanks, 1918
    Box/Folder 87: 3-4
  - Comité Suisse de Secours aux Serbes, 1917-1918
    Box/Folder 87: 5
  - Communications between the United States and Austria-Hungary, 1918
    Box/Folder 87: 6
  - Communications, Welfare inquiries, 1917-1918
    Box/Folder 87: 7
  - Communications with persons from enemy country, 1917-1918
    Box/Folder 87: 8
  - American Legation, Copenhagen, Allied prisoners, 1918-1919
    Box/Folder 87: 9
  - American Legation, Copenhagen, Americans prisoners in Germany, 1917-1918
    Box/Folder 87: 10
  - American Legation, Copenhagen, ARC, Berne, 1918
    Box/Folder 87: 11
  - American Legation, Copenhagen, ARC, Washington, 1918
    Box/Folder 87: 12
  - American Legation, Copenhagen, Appropriations, 1918-1919
    Box/Folder 87: 13
  - British Red Cross, 1918
    Box/Folder 87: 14
  - Danish Government, 1918
    Box/Folder 87: 15
  - Deserters, 1918-1919
    Box/Folder 87: 16
  - Donations and memberships, 1917-1918
    Box/Folder 87: 17
  - Ellis Loring Drésel, reports, 1916-1918
    Box/Folder 87: 18
  - Ellis Loring Drésel, reports, 1916-1918 (Reel 121)
    Box/Folder 87: 19
  - Henry C. Emery, correspondence, 1918
    Box/Folder 87: 20
  - Personnel, 1918-1919
    Box/Folder 87: 21
  - Exchange and interest, 1918-1919
    Box/Folder 87: 22
  - "Italian Evacuees," by Stanford University professor Henry R. Fairclough, 1918
    Box/Folder 87: 23
  - Financial Committee, minutes, 1918-1919
    Box/Folder 87: 24
  - Financial statements, 1918-1919
    Box/Folder 87: 25. See also oversized box 223
  - Geneva Chapter, 1918-1919
    Box/Folder 87: 26
  - Geneva Chapter, 1918-1919
    Box/Folder 88: 1-7
  - German Red Cross, 1918 (Reel 122)
    Box/Folder 88: 8
  - Commissioner for France Harvey D. Gibson, reports, 1918
    Box/Folder 88: 9
  - Herbert Hoover, U.S. Food Commission, Paris, France, 1918-1919
    Box/Folder 88: 10
  - Representative of ARC W.W. Husband, 1918-1919
    Box/Folder 88: 11
  - Individual inquiries, 1918-1919
    Box/Folder 88: 12
  - International Red Cross, 1919
    Box/Folder 88: 13
  - Interned students, 1917-1918
    Box/Folder 88: 14
  - League of Red Cross Societies, 1919
    Box/Folder 88: 15
  - Liffiol le Grand, 1919
    Box/Folder 88: 16
  - Medical Department, report, 1919
    Box/Folder 88: 17
  - Meetings of the ARC Commission, 1918
    Box/Folder 88: 18
  - Director of American Prisoners Relief Commission Athol Mclean, reports, 1918
    Box/Folder 88: 19
  - Commissioner for Switzerland John W. Mercer, correspondence, reports, 1919
    Box/Folder 88: 20-23
  - Organization of Camp Committee, 1918
    Box/Folder 88: 24
  - Paris Office, ARC, reports, 1919
    Box/Folder 88: 25
  - Personnel, 1919
    Box/Folder 88: 26
  - Prisoners of war, 1917-1922
    - General, 1918 (Reel 123)
      Box/Folder 89: 1-2
    - Italian prisoners, 1918
      Box/Folder 89: 3
    - Parcels to prisoners, 1918
      Box/Folder 89: 4
    - Christmas packets, 1918
      Box/Folder 89: 5
    - Bulk shipments, 1918
      Box/Folder 89: 6
    - Gustav Schneeli, correspondence, Munich, Germany, 1918
      Box/Folder 89: 7
    - Leon G. Levy, Department of Prisoners of War, Strasbourg, correspondence, 1918
      Box/Folder 89: 8
    - Northern camps, 1918
      Box/Folder 89: 9
    - National headquarters, Washington, D.C., 1918
      Box/Folder 89: 10
    - Endicott, Edenborough, London, 1918
      Box/Folder 89: 11
    - Military Attaché, U.S. Legation, Berne, General Andrews, 1918
      Box/Folder 89: 12
    - Commissioner for France Colonel H.D. Gibson, 1918
      Box/Folder 89: 13
    - American Legation at The Hague, Holland, 1918
      Box/Folder 89: 14
    - Director of Bureau of Prisoners Information and Communication Ralph E. Bailey, 1918-1919
      Box/Folder 89: 15
    - Major Ernest Shelling, Office of the Military Attaché, 1918
      Box/Folder 89: 16
    - Central Prisoners of War Committee, London, 1918
      Box/Folder 89: 17
    - Panamanian prisoners, 1918
      Box/Folder 89: 18
    - Serbian prisoners, 1917
      Box/Folder 89: 19
    - Amounts remitted to prisoners by international money-order, 1918-1919
      Box/Folder 89: 20
    - Drafts from ARC Washington for the prisoners, 1918-1919 (Reel 124)
      Box/Folder 89: 21
    - British Section, 1918
      Box/Folder 89: 22
    - Report of Bureau of Prisoner Information and Communication, Department of Prisoners of War, 1918
      Box/Folder 89: 23
    - Statement of money due to and from former prisoners of war as of, March 15, 1919
      Box/Folder 89: 24
    - Prisoners and refugees of war, 1920-1922
      Box/Folder 89: 25-27
    - Prison camps, general information, 1918
      Box/Folder 90: 1-2
    - Conferences, Berne, 1918-1919
      Box/Folder 90: 3-4
    - Conferences, Berne, 1918-1919 (Reel 125)
      Box/Folder 90: 5-10
    - Oeuvres, Berne, reports, 1918-1919
      Box/Folder 90: 11-12
- Commission for Germany, 1918-1921
  - American Expeditionary Forces (U.S. Army), 1919
    Box/Folder 90: 13
  - American Library Association, 1919
    Box/Folder 90: 14
  - Americans residing in Germany, 1919
    Box/Folder 90: 15
  - Berlin headquarters, 1919
    Box/Folder 90: 16
  - Bureau of Citizen Food Relief Service, Berlin, 1919
    Box/Folder 90: 17
  - Camps, 1919
    - Altenau
      Box/Folder 90: 18
    - Aschaffenburg
      Box/Folder 90: 19
    - Bautzen
      Box/Folder 90: 20
    - Bayreuth
      Box/Folder 90: 21
    - Berlin District (Camps)
      Box/Folder 90: 22
    - Berxen
      Box/Folder 90: 23
    - Brandenburg
      Box/Folder 90: 24
    - Clausthal
      Box/Folder 90: 25
    - Crossen
      Box/Folder 90: 26
    - Dülmen
      Box/Folder 90: 27
    - Eschwege
      Box/Folder 90: 28
    - Hannover
      Box/Folder 90: 29
    - Ingolstadt
      Box/Folder 90: 30
    - Königsbruck
      Box/Folder 90: 31
    - Meschede
      Box/Folder 90: 32
    - Minden
      Box/Folder 90: 33
    - Munich
      Box/Folder 90: 34
    - Munsterlager
      Box/Folder 90: 35
    - Sagan (Reel 126)
      Box/Folder 90: 36
    - Schneidemuehl
      Box/Folder 91: 1
    - Schöneberg
      Box/Folder 91: 2
    - Sennelager
      Box/Folder 91: 3
    - Soltau
      Box/Folder 91: 4
    - Spandau
      Box/Folder 91: 5
    - Springhirsch
      Box/Folder 91: 6
    - Stargard
      Box/Folder 91: 7
    - Ulm
      Box/Folder 91: 8
    - Wasbeck
      Box/Folder 91: 9
    - Wetzlar
      Box/Folder 91: 10
    - Wildeman
      Box/Folder 91: 11
    - Wünsdorf
      Box/Folder 91: 12-13
    - Würzburg
      Box/Folder 91: 14
    - Zerbst
      Box/Folder 91: 15-16
    - Zwickau
      Box/Folder 91: 17-18
  - Camps, Inspection trips to, 1919
    Box/Folder 91: 19
  - Canteens, 1919
    Box/Folder 91: 20-21
  - Civilian relief, 1919
    Box/Folder 91: 22
  - Clothing, 1919-1921
    Box/Folder 91: 23
  - Coblenz, 1919-1921 (Reel 127)
    Box/Folder 91: 24-25
  - Danish Red Cross, 1919
    Box/Folder 91: 26
  - Dresden District, general, 1919
    Box/Folder 91: 27
  - Dresden District, distribution of stores to Russian prisoners, 1919
    Box/Folder 91: 28
  - Finance--Expenditures in zone of occupation, 1918-1920
    Box/Folder 92: 1
  - Flour to be returned to German Government, 1920-1921
    Box/Folder 92: 2
  - Food drafts, 1919
    Box/Folder 92: 3
  - Food sold, 1919
    Box/Folder 92: 4-5
  - Hamburg, 1919
    Box/Folder 92: 6
  - Interallied Commission, General, administrative notes, nos. 1-50, 1919
    Box/Folder 92: 7
  - Interallied Commission, General, expenditures, statements, 1919
    Box/Folder 92: 8
  - Interallied Commission, General, reports, summary of weekly reports from senior allied officers on Russian prisoners of war camps, 1919
    Box/Folder 92: 9-10
  - Interallied Commission, food supply, 1919
    Box/Folder 92: 11-12
  - Interallied Commission, food supply, 1919 (Reel 128)
    Box/Folder 92: 13
  - Interallied Commission for the Repatriation of Russian Prisoners of War, general, 1918-1919
    Box/Folder 92: 14
  - Interallied Commission for the Repatriation of Russian Prisoners of War, Conferences--Berlin, 1919
    Box/Folder 92: 15-18
  - Interallied Commission for the Repatriation of Russian Prisoners of War, Conferences--Berlin, 1919
    Box/Folder 93: 1
  - Interallied Commission for the Repatriation of Russian Prisoners of War, Repatriation, 1919
    Box/Folder 93: 2
  - Senior allied officers at camps, orders and instructions, 1919
    Box/Folder 93: 3
  - Leipzig, 1920-1921 (Reel 129)
    Box/Folder 93: 4
  - Magdeburg, 1919
    Box/Folder 93: 5
  - Marienburg, 1919
    Box/Folder 93: 6
  - Mayence, 1919
    Box/Folder 93: 7
  - Major John W. Mercer, 1919
    Box/Folder 93: 8
  - Munich revolt, Prisoners of, 1919
    Box/Folder 93: 9
  - Nurnberg, 1919
    Box/Folder 93: 10
  - Lt. Col. Robert E. Olds, 1919
    Box/Folder 93: 11
  - Oppau Disaster, 1921-1922
    Box/Folder 93: 12
  - Paris Office, cables from Berlin, 1919-1920
    Box/Folder 93: 13
  - Prison camp reports, 1918-1919
    Box/Folder 93: 14-16
  - Prisoners of war, American, 1918
    Box/Folder 93: 17
  - Prisoners of war, Russian, 1917-1919
    Box/Folder 93: 18-19
  - Rations, 1919
    Box/Folder 93: 20
  - Reports, 1918-1919
    Box/Folder 93: 21
  - Stettin District, 1919 (Reel 130)
    Box/Folder 93: 22
  - Shoes supplies for Russian prisoners, 1919
    Box/Folder 93: 23. Includes photographs
  - Swiss Commission, American Red Cross, 1919
    Box/Folder 93: 24
  - Lt. Col. Carl Taylor, ARC, 1919
    Box/Folder 93: 25
  - Young Men's Christian Associations, 1919
    Box/Folder 93: 26
- Commission for Italy, 1917-1921
  - General correspondence, reports, 1917-1920
    Box/Folder 94: 1-2
  - Ambulances, reports, 1917-1918
    Box/Folder 94: 3
  - American Embassy, correspondence, 1918-1919
    Box/Folder 94: 4-6
  - "Financial Report to April 30th, 1917," by American Relief Clearing House in Rome
    Box/Folder 94: 7
  - Appeals, 1920-1921
    Box/Folder 94: 8-9
  - Appreciations, tribute to ARC, 1918
    Box/Folder 94: 10-12
  - Civil and military reports by Captain Nicolas R. Rhodes, Bologna, 1918
    Box/Folder 94: 13
  - Budget, appropriations, 1919-1920 (Reel 131)
    Box/Folder 94: 14
  - Campidoglio ceremony, 1918
    Box/Folder 94: 15-16
  - Child welfare, 1918-1921
    Box/Folder 94: 17-18
  - Civil affairs, 1918-1922
    - Periodical reports, 1918
      Box/Folder 94: 19-21
    - Correspondence, 1918-1919
      Box/Folder 95: 1
    - Summary of activities, 1918-1919
      Box/Folder 95: 2
    - Reports, 1920-1922
      Box/Folder 95: 3
    - Casa per Profughi di Guerra, Napoli, 1917-1918
      Box/Folder 95: 4
    - Report of work in Conegliano, 1918
      Box/Folder 95: 5
  - Clippings, 1918
    Box/Folder 95: 6
  - Contracts, 1918-1919
    - Ancona, college for children of men who died in the war, 1918
      Box/Folder 95: 7
    - Bologna, convalescent home for children, 1918-1919
      Box/Folder 95: 8
    - Lucca, school and dispensary, 1918
      Box/Folder 95: 9
    - Milan and Mantua, home for orphans and agricultural school, 1918-1919
      Box/Folder 95: 10
    - Milan, refugees home, 1918 (Reel 132)
      Box/Folder 95: 11
    - Milan, playground, 1918
      Box/Folder 95: 12
    - Volta Mantovana, home for orphans boys and agricultural school, 1918
      Box/Folder 95: 13
    - Rome, Amcross Club, 1918-1919
      Box/Folder 95: 14-15
    - Rome, Monteporzio, Perugia, Travi, agricultural schools for refugee boys, 1919
      Box/Folder 95: 16-18
  - Chairman of the War Council of the ARC Henry P. Davison, 1918
    Box/Folder 95: 19
  - History of ARC work in Italy, 1918
    Box/Folder 95: 20
  - History of ARC work in Italy, 1918 (Reel 133)
    Box/Folder 95: 21
  - Inter-office correspondence, 1918-1919
    Box/Folder 95: 22
  - Preliminary memorandum on Italy submitted by Lt.-Col Homer Folks, ARC, 22 January 1919
    Box/Folder 95: 23
  - Health condition, report by Colonel Gibson, undated
    Box/Folder 95: 24
  - Home Service Department, reports, 1918-1919
    Box/Folder 96: 1
  - Italian army, 1918
    Box/Folder 96: 2
  - Italian front, 1918
    Box/Folder 96: 3-4
  - Italian Government, 1918-1919
    Box/Folder 96: 5
  - Italian law, 1917-1918
    Box/Folder 96: 6-7
  - Genoa, reports, 1917-1918
    Box/Folder 96: 8
  - Junior Red Cross, 1919 (Reel 134)
    Box/Folder 96: 9-11
  - "Seven Weeks in Italy," by Paul U. Kellogg, Paris, 1917
    Box/Folder 96: 12-15
  - Department of Medical Affairs, reports, 1918
    Box/Folder 96: 16
  - Medical work, 1920
    Box/Folder 96: 17
  - Milan, civil and military affairs, 1918
    Box/Folder 96: 18
  - Department of Military Affairs, 1918-1919
    Box/Folder 96: 19-21
  - Commissioner to Italy Colonel E.O. Bartlett, 1919
    Box/Folder 96: 22
  - Miscellany, correspondence, reports, 1920-1921
    Box/Folder 96: 23
  - Miscellany, correspondence, reports, 1920-1921 (Reel 135)
    Box/Folder 96: 24-25
  - Miscellany, correspondence, reports, 1920-1921
    Box/Folder 97: 1-7
  - Military relief, 1920 (Reel 136)
    Box/Folder 97: 8-9
  - Padova district, reports, 1918
    Box/Folder 97: 10
  - Paris Office, 1918-1919
    - Correspondence, 1918-1919
      Box/Folder 97: 11
    - Directory of personnel, 1918
      Box/Folder 97: 12
  - Sardinia, reports, 1917
    Box/Folder 97: 13
  - Photographs (sent to Washington), list, captions, 1918
    Box/Folder 97: 14
  - Colonel Robert Perkins, correspondence, 1918
    Box/Folder 97: 15
  - Department of Public Information, reports to Washington, 1918-1919
    Box/Folder 97: 16-19
  - List of premises occupied by ARC, 1918-1919
    Box/Folder 97: 20-21
  - List of premises occupied by ARC, 1918-1919 (Reel 137)
    Box/Folder 98: 1
  - Prisoners and refugees of war, 1918-1919
    Box/Folder 98: 2-7
  - Reports, 1918-1922
    Box/Folder 98: 8-12
  - Reports, 1918-1922 (Reel 138)
    Box/Folder 95: 13-14
  - Short statements, 1918-1919
    Box/Folder 98: 15
  - Purchasing Department, 1918
    Box/Folder 98: 16
  - Accounting, 1919-1920
    Box/Folder 98: 17-19
  - Transportation, 1919
    Box/Folder 98: 20-21
  - Fratelli Luder Firenze, 1919
    Box/Folder 98: 22
  - Correspondence, 1918-1919
    - Alto Commissariato per I Profughi di Guerra, 1918
      Box/Folder 99: 1
    - Minister of War and the Italian Military Engineering Department, 1918-1919
      Box/Folder 99: 2
    - L'Iniziativa, 1918-1919 (Reel 139)
      Box/Folder 99: 3-7
    - Istituto Nazionale di Credito per la Cooperazione, 1918
      Box/Folder 99: 8
    - Professor Grisostoni Gaetano, 1918-1919
      Box/Folder 99: 9
    - Avvocato Augusto Guglielmo Tuccimei, 1918
      Box/Folder 99: 10
    - Department of Civil Affairs, Pisa Contract, 1918-1919
      Box/Folder 99: 11-13